{
    "id": "bbb72dcb0c7d46028798da19fa634fc7",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………………….. trying hard, she couldn’t finish the job.",
            "description": "Despite is a preposition. It is followed by a noun. In spite of is also possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "Although",
                "In spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. she worked hard, she didn’t get the promotion.",
            "description": "Although is used to connect two contrasting ideas. It is a conjunction and is followed by a clause.",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "Although",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… I knew no one at the party, I had a nice time.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas. It is a conjunction and is followed by a clause.",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "However",
                "But"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… my pleas for help, he didn't move.",
            "description": "In spite of is used to connect two contrasting ideas. It is a preposition.",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "However",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I insist that she …………………………… dismissed.",
            "description": "Should is not normally used in the clause after insist.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "be",
                "should be"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I recommend that the factory ………………………….. moved to another place.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "be"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He insisted …………………………. for the drink.",
            "description": "Insist is followed by on + ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "on paying",
                "to pay",
                "for paying"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. my childhood was full of misery, my adulthood is peaceful.",
            "description": "While is used to connect two contrasting ideas. Though is also possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "While",
                "As",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I went to a shop ………………………….. they sell dry fruits.",
            "description": "Where can mean in which. ",
            "answers": [
                "there",
                "where",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She worked hard ………………………… she might get the promotion.",
            "description": "We use so that and in order that to indicate purpose.",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "in order that",
                "in order to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. his stamina, he is a good athlete.",
            "description": "Due to is similar to because of.",
            "answers": [
                "Due to",
                "Despite",
                "In spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I tried scuba diving …………………………. my fears.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "despite",
                "due to",
                "however"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}